(Leonard:)Two can play this game. Penny...
- Get up.
- All right.
Nice that the people
who are Ionely on Valentine's Day...
(Raj:)...can come here tonight
and be together.
(Stuart:)Yeah, I'm really looking forward to it.
(Stuart:)In fact, there's no place
I'd rather be than here.
- Except on a date with anybody.
- Literally anybody.
(Raj:)You and I have so much fun hanging out.
(Raj:)If you were a girl,
all of our problems would be solved.
(Leonard:)What?
(Raj:)Think about it. We'd hang out,
we'd read comic books, we'd see movies.
(Raj:)It'd be like the best relationship ever.
- It does sound nice.
- Then I'd take you home...
(Raj:)...slip off your little, black dress
and pile-drive you into oblivion.
(Leonard:)What?